我不斷欺騙自己
I've been lying to me
試圖讓我相信
Tried to get me to see
我應該自由奔放
That I belong somewhere free
但是
But free
自由何意？
The meaning is gone
我只覺孤獨
I just feel alone
想留下來的念頭
My intentions to stay
很快就消逝不見
Have quickly faded away
不確定該說什麼
I don't quite know what to say
但，嘿
But hey
流淚也沒用
I know tears are loose
我沒有藉口
I have no excuse
看著那青
Watch as the blue
漸漸換膚
Changes its hue
我突然映出
I come into view
我沒有選項
I don't have to choose
因為想你，我同
'Cause I miss you, too
但我還在月球
But I'm still on the moon
我還在月球
I'm still on the moon
我好幾次想起來
Countless times I remember
一些亂湊的回憶
Memories made together
曾說過會待在那頭
Said I'd be there forever
那頭
ever
但現在
But now
眼下的雨
The rain in my eyes
正在這層
is floating in these
滿天星飄蕩
star-covered skies
看著那青
Watch as the blue
漸漸換膚
Changes its hue
我突然映出
I come into view
我沒有選項
I don't have to choose
因為想你，我同
'Cause I miss you, too
但我還在月球
But I'm still on the moon
我沒有選項
I don't have to choose
因為想你，我同
'Cause I miss you, too
但我還在月球
But I'm still on the moon
我還在月球
I'm still on the moon
還在月球
Still on the moon